http://www.gungear.com/privacy-policy

Attention: we are out of stock on All Ammo. We expect more stock within 4 weeks. Please call with any questions.
Our Store will Be Closed from October 17th - 25th for Restructring
We accept APO/FPO Orders! - Learn More
All Ammo Flat Rate $9 Shipping
My Cart
About UsContact UsBlogMy AccountTrack Order
Shop AllFirearmsHandgunsRiflesShotgunsCarbine / PistolAir GunsTasersAmmunitionAmmo by CaliberAmmo by ManufacturerHolstersInside Waistband (IWB)Outside Waistband (OWB)Thigh HolstersNylon HolsterFanny PacksTaser HolstersKnivesFoldingOut The FrontFixed BladeHatchetsKarambitPush DaggerSwordsHuntingSurvivalTrail CamerasMedical SuppliesHatchetsArcheryApparelGlovesHeadwearSunglassesHearing ProtectionShooting GlassesAccessoriesAK PartsAR PartsHandgunPacks & BagsBi-Pods / Tri-PodsCleaning SuppliesFlashlight & LaserGun CasesGun Safes & LocksMagazinesScopes /OpticsSightsTriggersSolar ChargerRifle SlingsSelf DefenseBlack Rifle CoffeeUpper ReceiversBallistic BackpacksSTIK N SHOOT MAGNETIC LIGHTPhantom Quick Draw HolsterNexbeltFanny Packs
Have any questions? Call Us!
512-818-2188
Home
>							Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Section 1 - What Do We Do With Your Information?
When you purchase something from our site, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address.
When you browse our site, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.
With your permission, we may send you emails about our site, new products and other updates.
Section 2 - Consent
How do you get my consent?
When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.
If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.
How do I withdraw my consent?
If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at info@gungear.com
Section 3 - Disclosure
We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.
Section 4 - Warhead
Our store is hosted on Warhead Inc. They provide us with the online website platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you.
Your data is stored through Warhead’s data storage, databases and the general Warhead application. They store your data on a secure server behind a firewall.
Payment:
If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then Warhead stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted.
All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover.
PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers.
Section 5 - Third-Party Services
In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.
However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.
For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.
In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.
As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.
Once you leave our website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.
Links:
When you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.
Section 6 - Security
To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.
If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption. Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.
Cookies:
"Cookies" are data files that are sometimes downloaded to your personal computer upon visiting our website which permits our server to identify your browser whenever you interact with the site.
We use cookies to recognize repeat visits to the site and to collect information about users' interactions. These cookies contain identification information that enables us to streamline many site features including the shopping and ordering experiences. You may set your browser software to reject cookies, but you may still be required to enter personal login information each time you access the website, and you may not be able to utilize certain website features. In some cases, you may not be able to access individual website sections or services if cookies are disabled.
Section 7 - Age Of Consent
By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.
Section 8 - Changes To This Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.
If our site is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.
Questions And Contact Information
If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact us at info@gungear.com
A leader is the man who has the ability to get other people to do what they don't want to do, and like it.
- Harry S. Truman
Sign up for our newsletter to stay up-to-date with our promotions, discounts, sales, and special offers.
Information About UsContact UsShipping & ReturnsPrivacy PolicyTerms & ConditionsPurchasing A FirearmFirearms Policy / Shipping
My Account My AccountOrder HistoryTrack OrdersAddress Book
ContactsAddress: 2207 N Main St, Taylor, TX 76574Phones: 512-818-2188Fax: 512-548-7655Hours: Mon - Fri 9:00 am - 5:00 pmE-mail: info@gungear.com
©
Gun Gear. All Rights Reserved. Designed by KREATIVE
Our website uses cookies to make your browsing experience better. By using our site you agree to our use of cookies. Learn More
I Agree
×
What Are Cookies
As is common practice with almost all professional websites this site uses cookies, which are tiny files that are downloaded to your computer, to improve your experience. This page describes what information they gather, how we use it and why we sometimes need to store these cookies. We will also share how you can prevent these cookies from being stored however this may downgrade or 'break' certain elements of the sites functionality.
For more general information on cookies see the Wikipedia article on HTTP Cookies.
How We Use Cookies
We use cookies for a variety of reasons detailed below. Unfortunately in most cases there are no industry standard options for disabling cookies without completely disabling the functionality and features they add to this site. It is recommended that you leave on all cookies if you are not sure whether you need them or not in case they are used to provide a service that you use.
Disabling Cookies
You can prevent the setting of cookies by adjusting the settings on your browser (see your browser Help for how to do this). Be aware that disabling cookies will affect the functionality of this and many other websites that you visit. Disabling cookies will usually result in also disabling certain functionality and features of the this site. Therefore it is recommended that you do not disable cookies.
The Cookies We Set
Account related cookies
If you create an account with us then we will use cookies for the management of the signup process and general administration. These cookies will usually be deleted when you log out however in some cases they may remain afterwards to remember your site preferences when logged out.
Login related cookies
We use cookies when you are logged in so that we can remember this fact. This prevents you from having to log in every single time you visit a new page. These cookies are typically removed or cleared when you log out to ensure that you can only access restricted features and areas when logged in.
Form related cookies
When you submit data to through a form such as those found on contact pages or comment forms cookies may be set to remember your user details for future correspondence.
Site preference cookies
In order to provide you with a great experience on this site we provide the functionality to set your preferences for how this site runs when you use it. In order to remember your preferences we need to set cookies so that this information can be called whenever you interact with a page is affected by your preferences.
Third Party Cookies
In some special cases we also use cookies provided by trusted third parties. The following section details which third party cookies you might encounter through this site.
This site uses Google Analytics which is one of the most widespread and trusted analytics solution on the web for helping us to understand how you use the site and ways that we can improve your experience. These cookies may track things such as how long you spend on the site and the pages that you visit so we can continue to produce engaging content.
For more information on Google Analytics cookies, see the official Google Analytics page.
We also use social media buttons and/or plugins on this site that allow you to connect with social network in various ways. For these to work, the social networks may set cookies through our site which may be used to enhance your profile on their site, or contribute to other purposes outlined in their respective privacy policies.
